welcome back to another shot cut video
欢迎回到另一个镜头剪辑视频
editing tutorial in this video we're
编辑教程在这段视频中我们
going to learn how to export our project
学习如何输出我们的项目
into a video or in any format we want so
转换成视频或任何我们想要的格式
to get started I'm just going to type in
开始之前 我只需输入
something here
这里有一些东西
I like test2 and hit start so I have a
我喜欢测试2并点击开始 所以我有一个
video project here just empty we'll drag
这里的视频项目是空的 我们会拖
in a couple I have some files on my
几个月后 我有一些关于我的文件
computer will drag in this one it will
计算机会把这个拖进来它会
also drag in this one I'll drag in a few
还有这个 我再拖几个
here pause this so now I have a couple
这里暂停一下 现在我有几个
different video files I'm going to drag
我要拖动的不同视频文件
just down to the timeline and in fact
就在时间线上 事实上
we're not gonna do the whole thing we'll
我们不会做所有的事情 我们会
shrink this way way way down by left
从这里往下向左收缩
clicking here at the end of the video
在视频结尾处单击此处
we'll take this down to just a couple of
我们将把这个归结为几个
seconds and then we'll grab this one and
几秒钟 然后我们抓住这个 然后
this way we're gonna we're gonna choose
这样我们就会我们会选择
our in and out point of the video here
我们视频的进出点在这里
and grab a few seconds of this and then
抓起几秒钟的时间 然后
this last one right there this last one
最后一个就在那里 这个最后一个
I'm going to will bring it in as well
我要把它也带进来
the whole thing and I'll just select a
整个过程 我只会选择一个
portion here and go split at playhead
在这里分 然后在PlayHead分
and we'll go split at playhead just so
我们会在PlayHead分道扬镳
we can see a few different ways there to
我们可以看到几种不同的方法来
adjust the size of our Clips so now we
调整剪辑的大小 这样我们就可以
have three different Clips in here and
这里有三个不同的夹子
make this a little bit longer okay we
把这个弄长一点 好吗？
have three video clips in our project we
在我们的项目中有三个视频剪辑
can play and see what this looks like
可以玩一下 看看这是什么样子的
it's a 4 second video clip alright
这是一个4秒的视频剪辑 好的
that's a fun video so we got about 4
这是一个有趣的视频 所以我们有大约4个
seconds of video here if we want to
这里有几秒钟的视频 如果我们想
export this now because we do have a
现在就出口 因为我们确实有
project we see when we're clicking on
当我们点击时看到的项目
project we have a timeline we have three
项目我们有一个时间表 我们有三个
video clips in a single video timeline
单个视频时间线中的视频剪辑
and there's also audio associated with
还有一段音频与
this video we can export this
这个视频我们可以导出这个
intuitively sometimes you people just
凭直觉 有时候你们这些人
think if you click file and go to save
想象一下 如果您单击文件并转到保存
it's gonna save your video that saved a
它将保存您的视频 从而保存了
test to MLT so it's saved a video
测试到MLT 这样就可以保存视频
project file that we can then open up
我们随后可以打开的项目文件
and they'll show it just like this
他们会像这样展示它
that's a good thing to do but that's not
这是一件好事 但那不是
a video we can play or upload to youtube
我们可以播放或上传到YouTube的视频
or share with friends to get an actual
或与朋友分享以获得一个实际的
video that we can share we need to click
我们需要点击可以分享的视频
on
在……上面
sport so we click export' here and it
体育 所以我们点击出口‘这里和它
brings up a new dialog over here it
在此处显示一个新的对话框
actually was already here by the way we
实际上我们已经在这里了
can toggle between playlists where we
可以在播放列表之间切换 我们可以
were looking at our different source
正在寻找我们不同的消息来源
files and export we can just toggle
文件和导出 我们只需切换
between there there's also filters
在那里之间也有过滤器
properties but right now we're on the
房产 但现在我们正在
export tab and so if that gets closed or
选项卡 因此如果该选项卡关闭或
for whatever reason that's not showing
不管是什么原因 它都没有显示出来
up for you just click export and it'll
为您打开只需点击导出 它将
appear somewhere in your interface but
出现在界面中的某个位置 但
probably here on on the left it gives us
可能就在左边 它给了我们
some options for how we want to export
我们想要如何导出的一些选项
this it says you know what do you what
这上面写着你知道你在做什么
do you want to do do you want it to be
你想做什么？你想要吗？
for YouTube you can click you to it has
在YouTube上 你可以点击它
a preset for that do you want it to be a
这是预置的吗？您希望它是
WebM file extension if you want it to be
如果您希望WebM文件扩展名为
just the mp3 just an audio file or we
只有mp3只是一个音频文件 或者我们
have all these different settings here
在这里有所有这些不同的设置
but for the most part if you know a
但在很大程度上 如果你知道
specific thing that you want you can
你想要的特定的东西你可以
explore some of these other ones down
向下探索一下其他一些
here but we're just going to do I
但我们现在要做的是
actually do a lot of this h.264 main
实际上做了很多H.264 Main
profile but I think it's very similar to
个人资料 但我认为它非常类似于
YouTube so I'm gonna click on YouTube
所以我要点击YouTube
and we'll use this as our profile so
我们会用这个作为我们的个人资料
YouTube is now selected all we have to
YouTube现在是我们所要做的一切
do is hit export file and it brings up
DO命中导出文件 它会调出
this dialog that says it says wear on
这个对话框上写着佩戴
your computer who you want to save it so
您要将其保存到的计算机
we'll just we'll call it test dot -
我们就叫它测试点吧-
let's save it under videos and we'll
让我们把它保存在视频下 我们将
call it test out - under videos and then
将其称为测试-在视频下 然后
hit save and it takes we see it
点击扑救 我们就能看到它
processing over here so it's rendering
在这里处理 所以它正在渲染
this video it's a 50% done now what it's
这个视频现在已经完成了50%
doing is just going through we didn't do
所做的只是经历我们没有做过的事情
money we just did some edits some splits
钱 我们刚刚做了一些编辑和拆分
is all we really did so it's done now it
就是我们真正做的一切所以现在就这么做了
didn't take too long and now I can open
没有花太长时间 现在我可以打开了
up on my computer and go to videos and I
打开我的电脑 打开视频 我
can find that video called test2 and we
可以找到名为Test2的视频 我们
can click play and we can play it
可以点击播放 我们可以播放它
let's see what that video looks like so
让我们看看这个视频是什么样子的
that's it just playing on the computer
那只是在电脑上播放而已
and that's an mp4 file so if we wanted a
这是一个MP4文件 所以如果我们想要一个
different file format we could choose
我们可以选择不同的文件格式
one of these other ones like maybe we
其他人中的一个 比如也许我们
want to burn it to a DVD and so I'm not
想把它刻录到DVD上 所以我不
quite sure actually how this will work
我很确定这将是如何运作的
if we can actually if we go to export
如果我们真的可以 如果我们去出口
file yeah here we go so this is going to
文件是的 我们开始了 所以这将是
be a dot VOB file so we hit save and now
是一个点VOB文件 所以我们点击保存 现在
it's just a different type of file
这是一种不同类型的文件
that's kind of formatted ideally for
这是一种理想的格式化方式
burning to a DVD that's gonna be played
刻录到要播放的DVD上
in North America NTSC if we want just
在北美的NTSC 如果我们只想
the audio portion we can click on this
我们可以点击音频部分
mp3 or WAV let's do mp3 and go to export
MP3或wav让我们做mp3 然后去出口
file and now it's going to be test -
文件 现在要进行测试-
dot-mpeg and that happened very quickly
Dot-mpeg 这发生得非常快
so now when we go to that directory I'm
所以现在当我们去那个目录的时候 我
on my computer under videos we see I
在我的电脑上的视频下 我们看到我
have an mp3 file it's just the audio
我有一个mp3文件 只是音频而已
portion of my video project see that and
我的视频项目的一部分看到了这一点
it's just playing in VLC player so
它只是在VLC播放器中播放 所以
hopefully that kind of makes sense
希望这是有意义的
there's lots of different ways you can
有很多不同的方法可以让你
export it's not just one video if you're
如果您要将其导出 不只是一个视频
not familiar with video formats there's
不熟悉视频格式 有
a lot of different video formats but
有很多不同的视频格式 但是
probably the safest thing for you to do
可能对你来说最安全的事
is just click this YouTube format and
只需点击此YouTube格式并
export it in YouTube if you're gonna be
如果你想把它输出到YouTube上
sharing this video on the web if you're
如果你想在网上分享这段视频
doing something more higher quality you
做一些更高质量的事情
might do like this h.264 high profile or
可能会像H.264这样高调或
some of these other different profiles
其中一些其他不同的配置文件
down here that maybe give you some more
在这里 可能会给你更多
detail and higher quality than just
细节和更高的质量
sharing online also if you're curious
如果你很好奇 也可以在网上分享
about these what's happening you can
关于这些正在发生的事情你可以
click on advanced and it tells you more
单击高级 它会告诉您更多信息
information about the codec being used
有关正在使用的编解码器的信息
about how the audio is being saved and
关于音频的保存方式以及
you can actually make changes to this
您实际上可以对此进行更改
too if you know what you're doing and
如果你知道自己在做什么
you can save it as you know different
您可以保存它 因为您知道不同
containers different audio different
容器不同音频不同
video formats but that's if you know
视频格式 但前提是您知道
what you're doing if not just click on
如果不点击 你正在做什么
YouTube and export file hopefully you
YouTube和输出文件希望您
found this video informative in the next
在接下来的视频中发现了信息丰富的
couple tutorials we're gonna be playing
我们要玩的几个教程
more with applying video and audio
更多应用视频和音频
effects working with multiple video and
处理多个视频的效果和
audio tracks in the same timeline so
音轨位于同一时间轴中
stay tuned for that
请继续关注
catch you in the next video
在下一个视频中与您联系